export const quizData = [
    {
        key: 1,
        question: "Question1",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
        key: 2,
        question: "Question2",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
        key: 3,
        question: "Question3",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
        key: 4,
        question: "Question4",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
        key: 5,
        question: "Question5",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
        key: 6,
        question: "Question6",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
        key: 7,
        question: "Question7",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
        key: 8,
        question: "Question8",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
        key: 9,
        question: "Question9",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
        key: 10,
        question: "Question10",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
        key: 11,
        question: "Question11",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
        key: 12,
        question: "Question12",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
        key: 13,
        question: "Question13",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
        key: 14,
        question: "Question14",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
        key: 15,
        question: "Question15",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
        key: 16,
        question: "Question16",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
        key: 17,
        question: "Question17",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
        key: 18,
        question: "Question18",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
        key: 19,
        question: "Question19",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "D",
    },
    {
        key: 20,
        question: "Question20",
        options: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
        correctAnswer: "A",
    },
];